One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Don't think that
you'll be able to survive...
after making the entire
world your enemy!
Bring it on!
Jump into the Waterfall!!
Plaza Outside the Courthouse
Left Tower
(Mozu and Lulu)
Okay! We pulled the lever!
We did it-waina!
Right Tower
(Kiwi and Tilestone)
Looks like Mozu and the
others got it done, too-waina.
Go, Straw Hat!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Looks like they pulled through.
Good timing.
I-I'm trembling with anticipation!
Lower that bridge already.
You look evil.
Robin!
We won't stop until we rescue you!
Stay over there!
They're in high spirits.
To think that they don't fear
the flag of the government...
How pointless.
There's no way
that they could defeat us.
Don't you cross!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Go! Straw Hat!
Curse those pirates!
Like we'd let that happen!
Get the mortar ready!
Stop the drawbridge!
Break it if you have to!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
This is the end of you!
Demolition Chop!
Chief Justice Baskerville!
Too bad!
We're actually
the chief justice trio!
What?!
I, the left Baskerville,
am named Bas!
I, the right Baskerville,
am named Kerville!
And I, the center Baskerville,
go by the name...
Princess!
What're ya talkin' about?!
So they were just stuck together?
What for?!
We're good friends!
Shut up!
Fire the mortar!
The drawbridge stopped?!
Gettin' in our way!
Those bastards!
Who did this?!
Chief Spandam!
Please evacuate
from the Tower of Justice!
All right! Good job!
I'm gonna head to the Gates of Justice
before they come over to this side!
Come, Nico Robin!
Someone! Bring Cutty Flam!
Robin!
Those pirates are nobodies.
I've got the assassin group
CP9 on my side!
Nico Robin, a survivor
of the island of scholars...
who schemed to bring back
the ancient weapons...
Cutty Flam, who inherited
an ancient weapon's blueprints...
I'm definitely not gonna stand back and
miss this opportunity to gain more power!
Cutty Flam...
That's...
Hey... don't tell me...
Those are the ancient
weapon Pluton's blueprints...!
They're the real deal.
Do you believe me?
Lucci... Kaku...
You guys can tell, right?
I thought it was unlikely...
So you were hiding them
inside your body, huh?
T-The real ones?!
Are those the real ones?!
Hand them over...
Hand them over to me!
Those are my long sought-after
blueprints!
Nico Robin.
Rumors are such unreliable things,
aren't they?
While we were being
brought to this damn place,
I came to realize
that you aren't some devil...
who's trying to misuse the weapon.
The Water 7 shipwrights haven't been passing down...
for generations just how to build the weapon.
Tom-san achieved
so many great things...
and gave up everything to preserve
these blueprints for the future.
At any rate, as long as there's a risk...
that a woman named Nico Robin
can restore the weapon,
the world needs
those blueprints to fight back.
Hey, Spanda.
What Tom-san and Iceburg
risked their lives to protect is...
Hand them over to me already!
the wish of this
weapon's architect—
that is, if the ancient weapon fell
into the hands of an idiot like you...
and started being used
to cause trouble,
the architect would want another weapon
to be built in order to stop it.
It's true that if you use Nico Robin,
you can revive the ancient weapon.
Even if she doesn't
want to help you,
as long as there's a chance
that she could be used,
she's still dangerous.
But she's got friends...
who are willing to risk
their lives to protect her.
So I'll...
take a chance!
I can think of only one way...
to uphold the architect's wish in this situation.
Just shut up and hand them
over to me already!
Those are mine!
You bastard!
What're you doing?!
It's burned to a cinder!
Dammit!
I'm gonna kill you!
Our five-year mission...
The blueprints were kept in order
to create a weapon to fight back...
And you, the government,
came after them a second time.
Essentially, something like
this should remain a secret,
and so once it's revealed,
it has to be eliminated.
Now, there's no longer a power to
fight back against the ancient weapon.
If nothing is done and Nico Robin
falls into your hands,
it'll be hopeless.
But if the Straw Hats win...
there won't be anything
left to you at all.
I made a bet on their victory.
How dare you mock me...?
Seems like you want
to die here, too, huh?
Bro!
Big Bro Franky!
Hey, look!
Bro is at the Tower of Justice!
Good! He's fine!
That's Bro-waina!
Bro!
We came to rescue you-waina!
We came with the Straw Hats!
Sodom and Gomorrah
fought hard, too!
Bro!
Come home with us!
Are you hurt?!
Y... You guys...
You idiots...
Who asked you to come...
to come rescue me?!
You idiots!
Bastards! I'm not crying!
Shut up, you bastards!
What are you, a demon?!
Robin's waiting!
Hurry up
and bring down the bridge!
Oh, yeah, right.
Hurry up, you bastards!
That's right!
Hurry up, you guys!
Or I'm gonna beat you up!
Y-Yeah, you're right.
I like when you're inconsistent
like that, too, Nami-san!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Looks like you looked out
for my underlings.
But this time,
I, their boss, the great Franky,
will add my super fighting power
to you guys!
Do what you want!
I'm still holding what
you did to Usopp against you!
Err... well,
he's right next to you...
Cutty Flam...
How dare you...
burn my blueprints?!
Ahh! Bro!
Bro is falling into the falls!
Franky!
Hey, pirates!
What?! Kokoro-san?!
I heard everything!
What're you guys wasting time for?!
Wasting time?
But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Halfway is good enough!
We'll be there in four seconds.
What the hell is that?!
Just dive in
toward the falls!
That's... from earlier...!
Is that the granny?
What does she mean?
I don't know.
But she said
jump toward the falls.
T-The sea train?!
Why is it in the courthouse?!
Chimney, go ahead and give that whistle a yank.
Okay!
That sounds like the sea train...
What's the meaning of that smile?
Chief Justice!
Please get out of here!
Stop!
Here we go!
I knew it!
Nooo!
Rocketman can still run!
Don't underestimate Tom's Workers,
the legendary shipbuilders!
R-Rocketman?!
It's flying again!
What?!
They're coming!
It's a waterfall!
This brings back memories,
doesn't it, Tom-san?
About helping that Roger guy...
I'm DAMN proud that I did!
I'm Luffy.
I'm the man
who'll be the pirate king.
Really?!
Yeah.
Roger...
was an idiot like this kid,
too, wasn't he?
And you helped him out.
Seems like we didn't learn our lesson.
Everyone in Tom's Workers
is helping this pirate kid.
You would've done the same,
wouldn't you, Tom-san?
We're gonna hit the wall!
W-We're gonna crash!
Run!
They're here...
They're here!
Dammit!
Hey, come with me!
If only I could get these
seastone handcuffs off...
Now, I'm letting you loose, CP9!
Beat the crap out of them
here, in the Tower of Justice!
I'll give you permission
to destroy them!
Lucci! Come with me!
Protecting my life is your
top priority!
Got that?!
Funkfreed!
All right, good boy.
Elephant Sword
Funkfreed
Elephant-Elephant Fruit
I've got this treasured sword,
in addition to CP9.
When I calm down and think,
I've got nothing to be afraid of.
Now, let's head to the Gates of Justice!
Go ahead and get this woman
back if you can, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Franky is okay!
The Straw Hats have finally
reached the Tower of Justice!
Bro is no longer a prisoner!
Looks like he's gonna join in the fight!
That's right!
He's that kind of person!
Get them, Bro!
Go! Straw Hat!
We're leaving the rest
to you, Straw Hat.
Hey, are you guys okay?!
Kokoro, you old hag?!
Little ones?!
What'd you come here for,
bringing out a dangerous thing
like Rocketman?!
W-Well, it saved me, too, but...
Hey! Hey, Old Hag!
Hang in there!
Hey! I beg you! Don't die!
Don't die!
I've got a nosebleed.
How could you walk away from this
sort of crash with just a nosebleed?!
All right! We're here!
Straw Hat...!
Hello!
Thanks, Monster Granny!
Hey, you guys!
Get up already!
That was nothing!
You're rubber. Don't lump us in with you.
Us flesh-and-blood humans were
forced to charge in like that.
You think we're okay...?
No way!
Yup, they're all fine.
You guys are all weirdos, too, so...
Just sayin'.
There are stairs over there!
Let's hurry up and catch up to Robin!
Wait.
What the heck is that?!
Chapapapa...
We have been invaded.
Even if you go
to the room you saw earlier,
Nico Robin isn't there anymore,
since Lucci took her to
the Gates of Justice.
What?!
Oh, and our chief is there, too.
Oh, is that right?!
Thanks for giving us
such valuable information.
Chapapa... I spilled the beans...
What a funny guy.
Oh, well...
They're headed there right now,
but I won't tell you how to get there,
and we, CP9,
won't let you go there, either.
We have an order to annihilate you guys.
Annihilation order...?
Unless you defeat us,
you won't be able
to set Nico Robin free.
Yeah.
You don't have to tell us that.
We're gonna do it anyway.
Chapapa...
What a high-spirited guy.
But let me tell you one more thing.
What?! Do as you wish.
Ah, thanks.
Then, I'll speak frankly.
Look at this!
A key?
What for?!
This is the key to unlock...
the seastone handcuffs on Nico Robin!
Seastone?
It's a stone that cancels out
devil fruit powers.
I heard that it's as effective as when
ability users fall into the sea.
So that's why Robin isn't fighting now,
despite how strong she actually is.
Yeah.
Under normal circumstances,
she isn't so weak that she'd helplessly
stay held captive by guys like that.
She must be feeling frustrated.
I see.
Even if you guys can rescue
Nico Robin by some chance,
since seastone
is hard like diamonds,
the handcuffs will be on her forever.
Chapapa...
I spilled the beans again.
He really is funny.
If that's okay, keep trying to
rescue Nico Robin.
Chapapapapa!
Well, then...
give that to us!
Looks like he can use
that technique, too.
Don't be so hasty.
I didn't say that this is the right key.
What?!
It might be...
for different handcuffs.
Chapapa papa!
There are five CP9 members,
including me, in this tower.
Each one has a key...
One, two, come on!
One, two, bad!
and is waiting for you.
Yow?!
Then, until we defeat you all
and get the keys,
and try them on Robin's handcuffs,
we won't know which one
is the right key?!
How stupid... buying time?
While we're fighting,
you guys are trying to take Robin-chan
to the Gates of Justice, aren't you?!
Quickly catching up with Robin
should be our priority.
We'll first get Robin back,
and then worry about the key.
Let's ignore that weirdo and hurry!
Chapa!
That weirdo
Chapapa!
You're smart.
But if you do that,
I'll ditch this key
into the sea! Chapapa!
We're giving you a chance.
See ya.
Ah! Wait, you jerk!
Hey, wait!
You wait, dammit!
Stop! Just a little bit longer!
Just wait until we decide
what each of us will do!
Ah! Let me go!
Calm down, Straw Hat-kun.
Let me go!
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's right.
If he's with Robin-chan,
we should let at least
Luffy go on ahead.
Luffy.
At any rate, you just
beat up the pigeon guy.
Let me go! Let me go!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
He said there are five CP9 members here.
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
It's all a race against time!
If we lose our fights,
it means we lose time!
Everyone! Win at all cost!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Pirate guys!
Chimney? Gonbe?
Where did they go?
They were there up until just a bit ago!
I'm sure I'll bump into them somewhere!
I'm not gonna let you go to
the Gates of Justice!
Robin!
Help won't come, Nico Robin.
They don't know how to get to the
Gates of Justice in the first place!
Come out! You pigeon jerk!
This is bad... before I fight...
Where's the kitchen?!
Coup de Boo!
Because I used a bottle and
a half of cola for Coup de Boo,
I've used more than two bottles today!
Unless I fill up all three bottles,
I can't fight CP9!
That area looks like a kitchen!
Chapapapapa...
I'm "Silent Fukuro"...
I like rumors!
Do you want the key?
Dammit!
I still haven't refilled my cola yet!
Chapa...!
No one was in there.
No one's here.
Hmm, or here.
All right, no one's here.
What's going on?
I can't find anyone anywhere!
If no one's around, that's fine, though.
They must've gotten scared of me...
Ahhh...!
Someone's here!
He's sleeping...
Is he part of CP9, too?
H-He's sleeping with the
key right in front of him!
Couldn't this be a huge,
lucky chance?!
I wonder what this
dungeon-like hallway is?
Yoyoi!
You damn pirate!
You're doomed now that
I've caught you here!
Wait...
a second...!
Yoyoi!
How annoying...
What about this room?!
Dammit...
No one's here, either.
Please make yourself at home.
Shall I... make some tea?
Yes, please!
You've already drawn your swords?
They're just
crying out for blood.